Guide to the Hanna House Collection SC0280
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Architectural Drawings
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 2 of 2, 1951-10-15; sc0280_059_02; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 1 of 3, 1951-11-28; sc0280_060_01; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 2 of 3, 1951-11-28; sc0280_060_02; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 3 of 3, 1951-11-28; sc0280_060_03; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 1 of 3, 1951-11-28; sc0280_061_01; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 2 of 3, 1951-11-28; sc0280_061_02; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 3 of 3, 1951-11-28; sc0280_061_03; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size detail of revised muntin on all sash, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_062; 19 x 39 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size detail of revised muntin on all sash, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_063; 20 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size detail of revised muntin on all sash, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_064; 20 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque Exhedra, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_065; 14 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque Exhedra, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_066; 14 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size detail of revised muntin on all sash, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_067; 20 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Delivery Box, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_068; 20.5 x 38.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Delivery Box, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_069; 20.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Sash schedule, House for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_070; 23 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Section H-H, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, 7,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_071; 21.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Lantern,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_072; 20 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Lantern,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_073; 20 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Lantern,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_074; 20 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_075; 26 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna House, Skylight over laundry, Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_076; 21.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna House, Skylight over laundry, Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_077; 21.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Carpet Layout, Hanna House, Palo Alto, Calif., Frank Lloyd Wright, 1937; sc0280_078; 16.5 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Garden pool, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_079; 21 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Garden pool, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_080; 21 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Garden pool, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_081; 21 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Caretaker's Apartment, Residence of Profesor and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Calif., Taliesin Associated Architects, Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation, 1974-8; sc0280_082; 18 x 27.5 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Caretaker's Apartment, Residence of Profesor and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Calif., Taliesin Associated Architects, Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation, 1974-8; sc0280_083; 18 x 27.5 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Caretaker's Apartment, Residence of Profesor and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Calif., Taliesin Associated Architects, Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation, 1974-8; sc0280_084; 18 x 27.5 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Study for Powder Room Mech. Room, Taliesin Associated Architects, 1974-10; sc0280_085; 18 x 27.5 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 1, 1950-5-12; sc0280_086_01; 24 x 35 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 2, 1950-4-24; sc0280_086_02; 24 x 35 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 3, 1950-4-24; sc0280_086_03; 24 x 35 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 4, 1950-4-24; sc0280_086_04; 24.5 x 35.5 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 5, 1950-4-24; sc0280_086_05; 24.5 x 35 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 6, 1950-5-12; sc0280_086_06; 24.5 x 35.5 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 7, 1950-7-3; sc0280_086_07; 24 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 8, 1950-7-24; sc0280_086_08; 24 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 9, 1950-6-13; sc0280_086_09; 9.5 x 24 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna Residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 10, 1950-7-5; sc0280_086_10; 10.5 x 24 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna Residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 11, 1950-7-10; sc0280_086_11; 24 x 24.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna Residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 12, 1950-7-18; sc0280_086_12; 24 x 30.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Addition to Hanna Residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 13, 1950-7-26; sc0280_086_13; 21 x 30 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldredge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose, Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 14, 1950-10-12; sc0280_086_14; 21.5 x 30 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 15, 1950-10-16; sc0280_086_15; 24 x 36 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Fence Repair Details for Forecourt fence, Hanna Honeycomb House, Stanford, California, 1980-5-30; sc0280_086_16; 24.5 x 35.5 inches; 1 stats (copies)
  - Fence Repair Details for Forecourt fence, Hanna Honeycomb House, Stanford, California, 1980-5-30; sc0280_087; 24 x 36 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect, Sheet 3, Furniture, 1957-4; sc0280_088; 18.5 x 24 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect, Sheet 3, Furniture, 1957-4; sc0280_089; 18.5 x 24 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Sanctum Fireplace Spit, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_090; 21 x 36 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - 235 Paul R. Hanna, copyright 1981 by George Mathew Stefan, sc0280_091; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Sketch of Planting by Hannas, 1937-1977, Hanna Residence, Frank Lloyd Wright, Peter Wright Shaw, Landscape Architecture, Environmental planning, 125 University Avenue, Palo Alto, California, 94301, 1980-4-3; sc0280_092; 36.5 x 41.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies), hand colored
  - Caretaker's Apartment, Residence of Profesor and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Calif., Taliesin Associated Architects, Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation, Plan Section, Sheet No. 1, 1974-8; sc0280_093; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Caretaker's Apartment, Residence of Profesor and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Calif., Taliesin Associated Architects, Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation, Plan Section, 1974-8; sc0280_094; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations at hobby shop, Hanna Honeycomb House, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Floor Plan Relf. Clg. Plan, Site Plan, A-1, Clark, Stromquist Sandstrom, Architects, 1982-5-18; sc0280__01; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations at hobby shop, Hanna Honeycomb House, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Elevations casework details finish schedule, A-2, Clark, Stromquist Sandstrom, Architects, 1982-5-18; sc0280__02; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations at hobby shop, Hanna Honeycomb House, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Details, A-3, Clark, Stromquist Sandstrom, Architects, 1982-5-18; sc0280__03; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations at hobby shop, Hanna Honeycomb House, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Electrical, E-1, Clark, Stromquist Sandstrom, Architects, 1982-5; sc0280__04; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations at hobby shop, Hanna Honeycomb House, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Original Plumbing Drawings for reference only, P-1, Clark, Stromquist Sandstrom, Architects, 1982-5; sc0280__05; 24 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Revised floor plan, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1, sc0280_096_01; 25.5 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Revised Dec. 7, 1936, initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 2, 1936-12-7; sc0280_096_02; 33 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Addition and alterations to "Honeycomb" House for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, 3, sc0280_096_03; 36 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - House for Dr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna, California, Frank Lloyd Wright Architect, Plot Plan, 4, sc0280_096_04; 29.5 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Screen between laboratory and living rm, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 5, sc0280_096_05; 35 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Full size details of all typical jambs, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 6, sc0280_096_06; 32.5 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Revised floor plan, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, ,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 7, sc0280_096_07; 22.5 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, 8, sc0280_096_08; 30 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Sections and Interior Elevations, Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, 9, sc0280_096_09; 37 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 10, sc0280_096_10; 31 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Full size detail of clerestory windows, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 11, sc0280_096_11; 31 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 12, sc0280_096_12; 22 X 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 13, sc0280_096_13; 28.5 X 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 14, sc0280_096_14; 30 X 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 15, sc0280_096_15; 32 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Garden wall, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 16, sc0280_096_16; 22 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 17, sc0280_096_17; 16.5 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Barbeque Exhedra, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 18, sc0280_096_18; 14 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Section A–A, Sash folding on track, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 19, sc0280_096_19; 35 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Garden wall, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 20, sc0280_096_20; 26.5 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 21, sc0280_096_21; 31 X 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Chimney Details, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, ,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 22, sc0280_096_22; 16.5 x 22 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Addition to House for Dr. Hanna, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 23, sc0280_096_23; 28.5 x 28.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Alterations for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 24, 1957-4; sc0280_096_24; 20 x 26 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Sanctum Fireplace and chimney, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 25, sc0280_096_25; 19 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Revised plan for concrete mat and brick work, Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 26, sc0280_096_26; 36.5 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Framing plan for flat roofs, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 27, sc0280_096_27; 36 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Details of Chimney and basement, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 28, sc0280_096_28; 25 x 39.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Details, Sheet 2, 29, sc0280_096_29; 26 x 36.5 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Section B-B, sc0280_096_30; 16.5 x 40 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Framing plan for flat roofs and decks, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 31, sc0280_096_31; 33.5 x 37 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 32, sc0280_096_32; 27 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright, Hanna House, sc0280_096_33; 37 x 42 inches; 1 diazotypes (copies)
- Microfilm, 7 microfilm reel(s) (Box 1)
  The seven microfilm rolls record three separate portions of the collection:
  1. Archives: Microfilm Rolls Nos.1 - 5.
  Fifty-three (53) binder volumes of correspondence with Frank Lloyd Wright and others, telegrarns, telephone notes, contracts, building specifications, financial transactions, and other items, covering a half-century from 1930 through 1981. Circa 6,000 pages of documents record the story of Mr. Wright's designing of the project, tile construction of several buildings - accomplished in five phases, the role of Stanford University, the public and architects' interest in the project, an evaluation by the clients, and many related aspects.
  Each item in the Archives (Vols. 1 - 53, microfilmed on Rolls 1 - 5) is numbered consecutively for each year. To illustrate: page number 360021 is read as follows, the first two numbers of the series (36) represent the year in which the document originated (1936); the last two numbers (21) indicate that this document is the 21st item prepared in the year; 790305 will be the 305th document prepared in 1979; etc.
  2. Photographs: Microfilm Roll No.6.
  Five albums of photographs of the original site, stages of construction, exterior and interior shots, furniture and fUrnishings. Over 500 photos taken by professional architectural photographers and by the clients.
  3. Drawings. Microfilm Roll No.7.
  184 sketches and drawings (mostly blueprints) by Frank Lloyd Wright, consultants, and the Hannas.
  An index to the microfilm is available online here: http://purl.stanford.edu/nd730bn4620
- House documentation, 1906-1989; Accession ARCH-1983-020
  - Renovation documentation, 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - The Clients' Report manuscripts (Box 2, Folder 1-8)
  - Lists of architectural and Frank Lloyd Wright books (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Duplicate material, 1937-1982 (Box 2, Item 11-22)
    Files arranged chronologically titled "Duplicates." These files contain architectural plans, newspaper articles, publications related to the Hanna House, and correspondence between the Hannas and Frank Lloyd Wright from 1937-1982.
  - Books, pamphlets, and magazines (Box 3, Folder 1-10)
  - Library campus messenger slips (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Instructions for operating house, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Clients' Report documentation (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - William James and Frank W. Abrams letters, 1906-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Insurance appraisal, 1974 Mar 11 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - History of Hanna-Honeycomb House (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Plaquing ceremony correspondence, 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Book dust jackets (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Books, pamphlets, and magazines (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
  - Audiovisual material, 1 audiotape reel(s)
    - Hanna House plaque ceremony, 1966-07-09; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 4, Item 10-11)
      3 tape recordings of plaquing ceremony of the Hanna House by the American Institute of Architects (AIA) as a Frank Lloyd Wright Memorial. An event of the Stanford Summer Festival, July 9, 1966. Recorded by Russell Hanna.
    - Plaque Ceremony of the Hanna House as Frank Lloyd Wright memorial by the American Institute of Architects, Stanford Summer Festival, 1966-07-09; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Designing Curriculum for Today's Children--To-Morrow's Citizens, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Non-Hanna House materials
      - Bayless Manning, talk # 2, Stanford Law School (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Preservation News, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Notecards with book titles (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - b/w photographs and negatives of Hanna House construction and completion, 1936-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    2 of view of house site, circa 1937 5 exterior shots of the house, circa 1937 1 exterior shot, 1960s 4 shots of living room, 1966 1 color shot of Paul R. Hanna in the living room by Leo Holub
  - Photographic reproductions of architectural drawings (16) from the collection (Box 5, Folder 2)
- National Register of Historic Places correspondence, 1977-1984; Accession ARCH-1983-138 (Box 1)
- Hanna, Paul R. correspondence, 1975-1976; Accession ARCH-1984-051
  - Futagawa, Yukio, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tanigawa, Masima, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Additional material, 1938-1983; ARCH-1987-143
  - Pamphlets, magazine clippings, seven microfilm reels with index. (Box 1)
  - Microfiche and event flyers (Box 2)
  - Negatives, contact prints, xerox copies of prints, permission to quote, permission to use photos, photo conservation bulletins. (Box 3)
- The Clients' Report manuscripts, Accession ARCH-1989-100 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6)
- Anniversary notebook, 1987-11-15; Accession ARCH-1989-125 (Box 1)
- The Hanna Residence Stanford: Drawings by Frank Lloyd Wright [negatives], Accession ARCH-1993-021; 3 volume(s)
  - Book 1: Drawings 1-42 (Box 1)
  - Book 2: Drawings 43-101 (Box 1)
  - Book 2: Drawings 102-187 (Box 1)
- Publications about Hanna House, Accession ARCH-1995-026
  - House Beautiful, 1963 Jan (Box 1)
- Hanna, Paul R. files on Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1982-1992; Accession ARCH-1997-189
  - Work file (correspondence, clippings, etc. re the house and the records in the Archives) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chair: loan to Milwaukee Art Museum (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Presentation: Why Frank Lloyd Wright? (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Presentation: Furnishing our Frank Lloyd Wright House (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - California for Preservation Action: correspondence re possible publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Presentation: Society of Architectural Historians (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Presentation: AIA Arizona Chapter Convention (Box 1, Folder 7)